I have to tell the story I have to tell
the story I'm going to record the story
I'm G to put it on the
YouTube okay so we were just talking so
some random person just like walked by
and they're looking they're looking in
they're like what I cannot wait I cannot
wait to freak people out this is why I'm
not replacing my teeth because it makes
it even more fun like people people see
me and they're like what is going on
over
there and true story I have a fun true
story to talk about this
so so I was I was sleeping in the back
of my apartment is area and I was
testing out all these new you know $3
$600 you know Mountain gear you know
winter winter sleeping bags I was
testing them out I was uh and I was you
know just sleeping randomly like right
on the on the grass and and so I slept
overnight on the grass right right
behind this is an apartment complex and
I'm on the grass and there was like
there's a body there laying there in a
sleeping bag and and and um and then you
know I went in and worked for the whole
day you know at this very high-paying
Tech job which nobody would know by
looking at me which is great I love it
and then and then
I and then I and then and then I I went
back out to take a nap because I'm old
and I need my afternoon nap right jaly
where's jaly to make fun of me he always
makes fun of me you need a nap old man
you know what he's right so I'm like
taking a nap in the back and I like got
in my sleeping bag and I'm laying in the
sleeping bag and I'm woken up from my
nap I was like excuse me sir and I look
up and I'm like there's shiny polished
shoes and there's like navy blue you
know you know pants I'm like oh and
there was a police officer standing over
me it was so funny he was like standing
over me like this it's like excuse me
sir excuse me
sir he excuse me sir excuse me sir can I
help you uh I'm like oh hi
officer it's a great day isn't I
seriously I start talking about the
weather and and I was like I was like
why you there's been a report there's
been a report that there is a homeless
person in the backyard here it's been
one of your neighbors has called in I
says um and I said oh I'm I'm just
testing I'm just testing this gear
because I'm getting ready to go on this
Trans American thing I'm getting ready
to go on this Trans American trip and
and he goes oh that's so cool and I was
like he's like well as you were then I'm
like I'm sorry to disturb you please you
know proceed with sleeping and I
couldn't I was like seriously I was like
talking to to a cop like laying on the
ground with my head like you could just
picture it with like a sleeping B I'm
like no sir it's fine I'm blah blah blah
and he's like okay well as you were and
then he wouldn't leave he just wanted to
talk to me he's like well yeah that's
that's exciting what are you going to do
with that and I'm like you know and I
was like groggy and tired I was like
rolling
around so I sat up in the sleeping bag
and I said okay this cop's not going
away so I sat there and I talked with
him he was a wonderful guy I mean he was
just the nicest guy and I could tell he
was like well gosh that's that's great
great you know I don't want to I don't
want to dissuade you from that and I
think he started realizing hey look I
did the I did the thing on accident I
did the thing I did the reactions on
accident it's probably the right time
it's like it's like my computers knows
better than me it's not my computer my
AI is like adding special specs for me
on automatically anyway the moral of the
story is police officers are
awesome oh hey look it's time for me to
wake up and start the morning morning
boost yeah there see there yeah
yeah uh dismiss all
right that's my story about being woken
up by a police officer while sleeping in
my backyard